<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" lang=”en”?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="CV.xsl"?>
<xsl:stylesheet version="1.0" xmlns:xsl="http://www.w3.org/1999/XSL/Transform">
<meta>
   <Title>Curriculum Vitae</Title>
   <keywords>developer, programmer, skilled</keywords>
</meta>
<nav>
   <a href=”AdaptativeCurriculum.xml”>Adaptative Curriculum</a>
   <a href=”d”>g</a>
   <a href=”c”>r</a>
</nav>
<curriculum>
<identification>
   <name>Eduardo</name> de Lima <lname>Gouvêa</lname>
   <selfInterview>Video Self-Interview //work in Progress</selfInterview>
   <personal><age id=”pAge”>28</age> <mesure >years</mesure> old, Single, no dependente.</personal>
</identification>
<contact>
<link href=”f”>LinkedIn
<email type=”personal”>isbr16@gmail.com</email>
Contact number (67)99841-0756
</contact>
<demo>
   <repositorie>My code demo - 
      <link href=”https://github.com/Dude42/Demos/”>C (ANSI)</link>,
      <link href=”https://github.com/Dude42/Demos/blob/master/”>C ++ (ANSI)</link>,
      <link href=”https://github.com/Dude42/Demos/”>CSS3</link>,
      <link href=”https://github.com/Dude42/Demos/”>HTML5</link>,
      <link href=”https://github.com/Dude42/Demos/”>Java ( J2EE )</link>,
      <link href=”https://github.com/Dude42/Demos/”>JavaScript</link>,
      <link href=”https://github.com/Dude42/Demos/”>Pascal</link>,
      <link href=”https://github.com/Dude42/Demos/”>PHP5</link>,
      <link href=”https://github.com/Dude42/Demos/”>Python3.5 (Twitter API)</link>,
      <link href=”https://github.com/Dude42/Demos/”>R(TweetR, XTS)</link>,
      <link href=”https://github.com/Dude42/Demos/”>Scala2.0</link>,
      <link href=”https://github.com/Dude42/Demos/”>SQL (PL / SQL)</link>,
      <link href=”https://github.com/Dude42/Demos/”>Swift</link>,
      <link href=”https://github.com/Dude42/Demos/”>XQuery1.0</link>
   </repositorie>
   <language>Text Reading Samples(hosted on YouTube):
      <link href=”https://youtu.be/cNpqE9xR3DY”>| English <expand>+</expand>
      <link href=”f”>| Espanol <expand>+</expand>
      <link href=”https://youtu.be/i3edVcoS3fg”>| Français <expand>+</expand>
      <link href=”f”>| Português <expand>+</expand>
 |
   </language>
</demo>

<interest>
   <professional>Professionally able to work with
      <skill>Agile
      <expand>- Capability Maturity Model, Continuous Delivery (DevOps), eXtreme Programming, Kanban, LeSS, Scrum</expand>
      </skill>
      <skill>Business Intelligence
      <expand>- Capex Opex, Client Relationship Management, Enterprise
Resource Planning, Systems Integration</expand>
      </skill>
      <skill>Computer Networks
      <expand>- Broadcasting, LISP Architecture, RM-OSI, Software-Defined
Networking, TCP / IP, Topology, UDP</expand>
      </skill>
      <skill>Cryptology
      <expand>- Algorythms (Hashing, RSA, SHA, Cesar's Cipher, Transposition
Cipher, Huffman Code), Cryptoanalisis</expand>
      </skill>
      <skill>Data Base
      <expand>- MySQL (memcached), PostgreSQL</expand>
      </skill>
      <skill>Data Security
      <expand>- Access Control, Authentication, Auditing, Autorization,Backup, Sandbox</expand>
      </skill>
      <skill>Data Science
      <expand>- Kappa Architecture, Minning Data, Lambda Architecture, Statistics, Zeta Architecture</expand>
      </skill>
      <skill>Data Structures
      <expand>- Dictionary, Batteries, Distributed File Systems, General Theory of
Systems, Lists, Microdata, Pooling, Registers, Service Oriented Architecture, Tuples, Trees ( AVL, Binary, Rubro-Black, Graphs)</expand>
      </skill>
      <skill>File Systems
      <expand>- Network File System, Journaling, Ext(2,3,4), BTRFS<expand>
      </skill>
      <skill>Forensycs
      <expand>- Proof Acquaring, Proof Analisis</expand>
      </skill>
      <skill>Frameworks
      <expand>- Apache Spark, Enterprise Java Beans, Hibernate, JIRA, Symphony2</expand>
      </skill>
      <skill>Governance - Control Objectives for Information and related Technologies,
Information Technologies Infrastructure Layer,
      </skill>
      <skill>Graphic Development - 3D Modeling (blender), Image Editing (basic Gimp and Krita)
      </skill>
      <skill>Hardware - Field Programmable Gate Array, Harvard Architecture,Logic Circuits (vhdl), Maintenance and Assembly for Desktop and Workstation, Parts Market, Sparc (V9), Von Newman Architecture
       </skill>
       <skill>Integration - ODBC, Oracle Golden Gate
       </skill>
       <skill>Laws, Rules and Standards - Copyright, Software Licenses (BSD, MIT, Apache, GPLv2, GPLv3, OSL, Creative Commons), Software Law, Patent Registration (INPI), RFC (7426,8201), ISO 14001:2004
       </skill>
       <skill>Object Orientation - Classes, Polymorphism, Heritance, Encapsulation, Templates, Nesting
       </skill>
       <skill>Office - Microsoft Office (Word, PowerPoint, Excel), Libre Office, WPS, Dashboard, Operating Systems - Ubuntu (Workstation,) OpenSUSE (KVM / QEMU), Windows 98 / ME / XP / 7 / 8 / 8.1 (Desktop), Android 6 / 7.1, FreeBSD 10, Red Hat Enterprise Linux 6.0(security)
       </skill>
       <skill>Philosophies - KISS, Bazaar, Scheduling, Kaizen, Ferengi Rules of Acquisition
       </skill>
       <skill>Quality Methodologies - Total Quality, Software Development Security, 5S
       </skill>
       <skill>Quality Testing - Authentication, Authorization, Availability, Confidentiality, Integrity, Mobile Device Management, Non-Repudiation
        </skill>
        <skill>Shell – Bash, Ksh, Csh
        </skill>
        <skill>Sound Development - LMMS, Muse (basic)
        </skill>
        <skill>System Analysis - UML, Structogram, Flowchart, Organization Chart, LifeCycle Development Software, Structured Analysis, Continuous Integration, Bottom-Up Analysis, Architecture Balancing Composition, Top-Down Analysis
        </skill>
        <skill>Virtualization - Cloud, Virtual Machine, Emulation
        </skill>
        <skill>Web - Web Service, Service as a Service, Cloud Trends
        </skill>
        <future>Areas in which I want to acquire knowledge: IA, Deep Learning, Bioinformatics, Machine Learning.</future>
   </professional>
   <personal>
Hobbies: bilhar (1994-2007), videogames (1996-), reading (1998-), domino (1998),
truco(2002-), table RPG master (2002-2003,2008), keyboard(2004-2007).
     <future>if i could: alpinismo, paintball, </future>
     </personal>
</interest>
Communication Capabilities:

<language id=”langEN”>English (fluency - 70%, pronunciation - 50%, vocabulary - 30%)
</language>
<language id=”langFR”>French (fluency - 30%, pronunciation - 40%, vocabulary - 5%)
</language>
<language id=”langJP”>Japanese (fluency - 40%, pronunciation - 50%, vocabulary - 5%)
</language>
<language id=”langPT”>Portuguese: Native(grammar - 50%, oratory - 85%, vocabulary - 70%)
</language>
<language id=”langSP”>Spanish (fluency - 30%, pronunciation - 50%, vocabulary - 45%)
</language>
<future>Next german and italian.</future>

Professional Experience:

Barman 1998-2007,informal.
*Panfleteiro 2003, half period, for just one month in winter vacation.
*Horticultor 2008, 2013-2014, informal.
*Mason assistent 2017, 3 months, informal.
<education>
   Education:
   <courses>
   <professional>Self-taught - <I don't have neither goal nor limite to what i should learn, i just keep learning!</
      <institution>CIPS</institution> <city>Bauru</city>-<state>SP</state> <courses>Auxiliar Administrativo, Secretariado<courses> •2007
   </professional>
   <regular>
      <institution>School E.E. Azarias Leite</institution>
      <address><city>Bauru</city>-<state>SP</state></address>
      high school complete 2007
   </regular>
   *Musical School Renata <city>Bauru</city>-<state>SP</state> •Keyboard 5/6 modules •2004-2007
   *UNESP <city>Bauru</city>-<state>SP</state> •Palestras de Astronomia
   </courses>
</education>
<hiring>
   Hiring Conditions:
   <availabilities>
   -->Availabilities
   Interested in evaluating and acquiring certificates as soon as I am able to do so.
   Available to effective in up to 48 hours (time to move).
   <travel>Available for domestic travel and interested in taking visa wherever it is needed.</travel>
   Interested in living near the workplace.
   Available for overtime and hour bank when needed.
   <interview>Interview via online only ( textchat, audiochat, e-mail).</interview>
   </availabilities>
   -->Remuneration
   Salary R $ 6,000.00+ ( including commission and other types of monetary benefits, not related to vouchers, insurance and covenants), recognition of my activities in both quality and productivity, as a basis for promotion and salary increase.
   <contract>Contract: CLT with a minimum duration of 3 months.</contract>
</hiring>
<diferencial>✳ Stands for my learning, adaptability and creativity skills.</diferencial>

<FAQ>
   <commentary>
Intentionally some lines are left unfinished in first section, as there is learning in progress and content will be added to the area. I intend to focus my study attention on the area for which I will be hired, but without neglecting the others.
This documment is in fact an continous development and integration exercise, and layout here in is merely in a test envirionment, keeping my matunebility easy and changing to catch more attention.</commentary>
   <questions>
   FAQs
      <question>Do where you are from?</question>
      Bauru-SP
      <question>Where you are now?</question>
      Caracol-MS
      <question>What means that long list of ‘looking for work with’?</question>
      I look for anything matching any combo of that list, i am not sure about how far restrictive CREA regulations got, more generic than that description, just if they used a term like “computer guy”.
      <question>If we request you to develop some new skills to fit in the job requirements, how long you think you will took to learn it?</question>
      Week to month, deepends on the level requested and the number of topics( average assimilating 300~500 pages week ).
      <question>Which is the best and should be preferable way to contact you?</question>
      By E-mail, i don’t own a cellphone number now, providing one relative number when must be placed.
   </questions>
   <notes>
   Note: Hidden usefulness
      <note>Like Role Playing Game master i got selfconfidence about my leadership to apply for high ranks, cause RPG masters must be able to create challanges and convice players to solve them having fun.And i created my own campaings, keeping control above requirements, flux, and objectives without suport matterial or tricks to reduce players freedom, allowing they to choose maximum possibilities that i could handle.</note>
      <note>Like barman, i got earlier about client behavoir, interest, and satisfaction. Keep an eye on them is essential to bussiness success, and this was a decisive factor to face our *concorrentes.</note>
   </notes>
<feedback>Please feel free to reply any feedback to my mail: critics, questions, job offers, so on…</feedback>
</FAQ>
</curriculum>
</xsl:stylesheet version="1.0" xmlns:xsl="http://www.w3.org/1999/XSL/Transform">
